http://www.vitalhealth.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy | Vital Health Endometriosis Center
Skip links Skip to primary navigation Skip to contentPhone: (408) 358-2511FAQPatient PortalPatient FormsContact
Laparoscopic Diagnosis
Other Conditions (Co-Conditions)
Adenomyosis
Adhesions
Pelvic Floor Dysfunction
Painful Bladder Syndrome (Interstitial Cystitis)
Endometriosis Information Center
Important QuestionsWhat is Endometriosis?What it Really Means to Have EndometriosisWhy is Excision More Effective in Treating Endometriosis than Other Surgical Techniques?What is the Purpose of Endometriosis Surgery?Why is Surgical Excision Only Practiced by Select Surgeons?Is My Pelvic Pain Endometriosis?Is Surgical Excision Optimal for the Treatment of All Areas of Disease?What are Adhesions and how are they treated? Endometriosis EducationIs There a Cure?What Causes Endometriosis?Endometriosis SymptomsEndometriosis Treatment OptionsIntegrative TreatmentWhat is Hormone Therapy?Dr. Cook’s Books The ScienceHow to Properly Treat EndometriosisOutcomes from SurgeryEndometriosis SurgeryWhat is Wide Surgical Excision?Laparoscopic DiagnosisEndo Blog
Review My Case
Privacy PolicyHomePrivacy PolicyYour privacy concerns are important to vitalhealth.com. Our Privacy Policy is designed to protect your Personal Information while providing the services available on our website. Vital Health Endometriosis Center will not give or sell your information to a third party. You may use the vitalhealth.com website without giving us specific Personal Information that identifies you.“Personal Information” includes, but is not limited to name, address, telephone number, e-mail address and similar information.Personal Information is collected only if you voluntarily provide it on the website, however, certain information may be required to complete some services provided. If you do not wish to provide the information requested on a screen, or if you have concerns about maintaining the confidentiality of any information, do not provide it. Vital Health Endometriosis Center is using AdWords’ free conversion tracking feature but Google does not record or use the user’s personal data in any way.We will use Personal Information provided by you on a voluntary basis for the purpose for which it is given to us. It may be used by vitalhealth.com, or by entities with which we contract for such purposes, which are disclosed at the time the information is given. If at any time you do not feel fully confident about the information you are providing, please feel free to contact us.If you visit a website linked to the vitalhealth.com website, you should consult that website’s privacy policy before providing Personal Information.In making your decision whether to provide Personal Information, you should be aware of the general risks of transmitting information over the Internet. While vitalhealth.com attempts to prevent unauthorized persons from accessing or tampering with our website, we cannot guarantee that these efforts will always be successful.SummaryArticle NameVital Health Privacy PolicyDescriptionYour privacy concerns are important to vitalhealth.com. Our Privacy Policy is designed to protect your Personal Information.
Search for:
Connect With Us
DisclaimerThe content contained in this web site is for informational use only and is not intended as medical advice. You should always seek the advice and care of your local physician. Information on this web site is also subject to change without notice and may include technical inaccuracies or typographical errors.Vital Health Endometriosis Center is an international treatment center located in Los Gatos near San Jose, California and specializes in endometriosis and chronic pelvic pain. Women travel from throughout the U.S., Canada and countries worldwide to the San Francisco Bay Area for treatment by Dr. Andrew Cook and his dedicated, professional staff. Endometriosis ResourcesEndometriosisPelvic PainAdenomyosisAdhesionsPelvic FloorPainful BladderAbnormal BleedingLaparoscopic Diagnosis Out of Area PatientsVirtual ConsultsTraveling for CarePlan Your TreatmentTreatment TimelineTake a Virtual TourEndometriosis: Symptoms, Treatment and Causes Contact UsVital Health Endometriosis Center14830 Los Gatos Blvd., Suite 300
Los Gatos, CA 95032-2025Phone:408-358-2511
1-888-256-7705Request an AppointmentSite Map | Privacy Policy | Terms | Copyright © 1996-2019 Vital Health Endometriosis Center. All rights reserved. | Web Design by WorldLight Media
